RICHARD BUCCOLA: Hi, this is Rich Buccola of New York City.
All right, we're almost done.
I'm making sure this is just nice and smooth that it didn't get any lumps from your flour.
Just make sure you do that.
Just going to keep spreading that all around nice.
What we're going to do now is just add this right to our mixture of beef and onions and mushrooms, like so.
Yes, this is so good.
Let's just give that a good mix.
I'm going to put that under a low flame and let it thicken up.
And what happens now, we're going to boil some water for our noodles.
It's almost time for dinner.
We've just tasted a little bit of it and it's amazing, but we want it to thicken up a little bit so I have it on a very low flame.
And while my water starts to boil in my saucepan for our noodles, I'm just going to occasionally stir it.
And when I actually take this off the heat, it will really thicken up and be a really nice sauce.
It tastes amazing.
It tastes a little bit of the wine.
It's really good.
I hope you guys make this.